Adams, Leonard P. Papers /3046
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Adams/Proposed Airline Study -- Field Projects Directory. (Box 36)
  - Brooks Project, 1954-1960 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo Project, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Building, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Bulletin on Young Workers (New Project), 1959 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Burling Hospital Project, 1952-1955 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Christie, Robert A., 1950-1957 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Christie Project, 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Christie Lawsuit, 1954-1963 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Christie, Robert Movie Project, 1949-1954 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Robert A. Christie - Evidence, 1954-1956 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Chutroo File, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Norman Coates Thesis Project, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Communications Workers of America, Project, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - David Cole Lectures, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Cook Project, 1954-1960 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Corning Glass, 1951-1953 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Coxe Project, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Cullen: The St. Lawrence Seaway, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Daniel Project, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Directory (American Companies with Foreign Operations), 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Distribution Center Files, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Doherty: Teaching Industrial Relations, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Douglas Mediation Project, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Emerson, Lynn A. -- Writings, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Emerson, Lynn Instruction Materials Laboratory, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Evans Project, 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Wm. Feldesman, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Field Projects Directory, 1961-1963 (Box 36, Folder 47)
- Fitch/National Council of Churches -- Jury Duty Study. (Box 37)
  - Fitch- National Council of Churches, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Labor - General, 1956-1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - French Project File, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Galvin Project File, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Gilpatrick File, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Givens, Meredith B., 1950-1957 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Givens: Syracuse Manpower-Labor Market Study, 1941-1950 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Goil Project File, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Stephen Goodman, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Greenbaum Project File, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - William Greenbaum Project File (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Handbook on Human Resources & I & LR - NYS, 1953-1955 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Handbook Trade Union Organizations, 1951-1953 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Harris Project, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Hepton Project File, 1962-1966 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Hill Research Project, 1952-1955 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Dave Hyatt Project, 1960-1967 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - ILR Review, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Training Abstracts, 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - International Studies, 1954-1957 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Fraser Isbester, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Iszard Project File, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Jain Project File, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - James, Ralph - Research Project, 1954-1957 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Jamestown Project, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Janel Bulletin, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Pr. File -- Jeffrey, N., 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Jehring, J.J. Audio Visual Materials, 1950-1956 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Jenks Manuscript, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Jenkins Manuscript, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Jensen Longshore File, 1954-1958 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Jewelers Union, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Jones, Dallas, 1953-1956 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Jones, Galen - Study of Labor Periodicals, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Joseph Joy, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Jury Duty Study, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Kaufman/Railway Labor Legislation -- C. Brian Williams. (Box 38)
  - Kaufman - Railway Labor Legislation, 1954-1957 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - William J. Kilberg File, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Kirkwood, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Kramer Project File, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Kouzian Project, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Labor Education Project, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Jack Leonard Project, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Elmer Luchterhand, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lyons, Richard -- American Association for Labor Legislation, 1951-1953 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - McConnell, Social Security Project, 1953-1956 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - McFarland -- Special Report of Research Findings in United Electrical, Radio, etc. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - McGinn Project File, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Martin, Albert, 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Miller, J. Gormly Labor Management Documentation, 1949-1955 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Montgomery Article (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Mullady - Philomena, 1948-1954 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Murray Project File, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Naas -- American Labor Union Periodicals, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Sandra Nitidihardjo, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Spinks, Geoffrey, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Union Structure Study (Beirne), 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Royal Montgomery File, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Wage Determination Study - W. Howard, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - C. Brian Williams, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 24)